Seunghun Bang

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Details

HELSINKI

Finland

+821084183865

upi21x@gmail.com

Links

Portfolio Website

Github

Skills

React.js

Next.is

Strapi

JavaScript

TypeScript

Tailwind CSS

Liquid.js

webflow

Git

SCSS/SASS

Node.js

Redux

SQL

HTML5

CSS3

Bootstrap

React Native

Languages

English

Finnish

Korean

Japanese

Profile

Front-end developer with an attitude to always improve, interested in data visualization.

I have experience in operating UI/UX for customers by taking charge of various api / Review & Email plugin integrations on the Shopify platform, understanding the importance of responsive design, and experiencing increased sales through Google A/B testing.

Employment History

Frontend Developer, Rens Original, HELSINKI

NOVEMBER 2021 - MAY 2022

My job is to be responsible for connecting APIs of rens original's e-commerce website Review (Judge.me)/Nudgify/Shipping plug-ins, upgrading website content, landing page for new products (NFT/Hoodie/Shoes) and creating an updated UI/UX (Sidebar/Navbar/Slider) based on LiquidJS.

I encountered customer complaints and learned the way to approach the problems and it led me to fix size charts logic and issues related to reviews.

In addition to general communication between developers/designers/project managers, the sales data table of the Finance team was distributed to the Google Cloud server through the API of the Shipping Plugin, which the Logistic team uses. This experience provides valuable collaboration experience with other teams.

A/B testing using Google Optimize. I have compared and analyzed sales by giving changes to Hero Text, and have increased sales as a result.

By producing a large frame through webflow, a CMS service, we were able to increase productivity and quality on the landing page, successfully announced the start of a new product, and contributed to the company's first NFT sold-out.

Software Developer Intern, Beesh Oy, HELSINKI

JULY 2021 - OCTOBER 2021

While creating a company landing page using React / Bootstrap, I learned how to discuss the direction for problem solving with the designer and project manager. It was a good experience to understand the position of different job groups. It was produced by discussing the large framework of the landing page with other developers while keeping the deadline within the basic company discipline.

Freelance Interpretor at SLUSH (KR-EN), KISED (Korea Institute of Startup and Entrepreneurship Development), HELSINKI

NOVEMBER 2022 - NOVEMBER 2023

Along with Korea's representative startups selected by KISED under the Ministry of Small and Medium Business of Korea, I introduced the representative products and businesses of the companies as an on-site interpreter at the SLUSH booth, and arranged meetings between Korean CEOs, investors and collaborators. did

Freelance Interpretor (KR-EN), BWF (Badminton World Federation), Vantaa

OCTOBER 2021 - OCTOBER 2021

I translated pre-interview of the upcoming matchs before beginning of the competition and on-site interpretation for the Korean national team game. In addition, I was responsible for after-match interview of Korean players through real-time broadcasting of the national match in Vantaa.

Education

Bachelor, Haaga-Helia UAS, Helsinki

SEPTEMBER 2016 - APRIL 2023

In the Department of Business IT, I learned communication to solve problems through team assignments. By having time to build a prototype for real-time used application as well as basic programming knowledge, I was able to not only systematically learn UI/UX knowledge of web/apps used in reality but also programming as Javascript, React, NodeJS and etc, which helps me build a real-life solution for myself.